So your first sexual experience
was with a woman?
I was 15.
It was my best friend, Ruth.
And we got drunk on that hard cider.
And then suddenly,
we were making out.
Tell it again.
Seriously.
Can that woman talk
about anything else but sex?
Yeah, sure. Earlier she was
talking about geography.
She was listing the countries
she's done it in.
I think we all
learned something.
Hey, you guys! Look what I found!
That's my mom's writing. Look.
"Me and Frank and Phoebe,
graduation, 1965."
-Do you know what that means?
-That you're actually 50?
That's not "me" Phoebe.
That's her pal, Phoebe.
According to her yearbook,
they were BFF.
Best Friends Forever.
That's great!
I know! She probably has all kinds
of stories about my parents.
She might know where my dad is.
I looked her up.
She lives by the beach.
Maybe this weekend we can
go there.
-Shoot, I can't go. I have to work.
-That's too bad.
Big fat bummer.
So tomorrow we'll drive out
to Montauk.
Hey, Bonnie had sex there!
The One At the Beach
Would you look at them?
I'm never gonna find
a boyfriend again.
I'm gonna die an old maid.
You're not gonna die an old maid.
Maybe an old spinster cook.
-Thanks.
-Besides, worse comes to worse...
... I'll be your boyfriend.
Yeah, right.
Why is that so funny?
You made a joke, right?
So I laughed.
A little too hard.
Am I not boyfriend material?
You're Chandler.
You know. Chandler!
Okay, so we've established
my name, and hit me.
But say we weren't friends.
Say it's a blind date.
I show up at your door and I'm,
like, "Hey, nice to meet you."
I'd probably be scared of a guy
using a fake voice.
Oh, good. You bought food.
No, just my luggage.
I am having the best karma this week.
I find this woman
who knew my parents...
...and then my client
gives me his beach house.
What about that bike
messenger you hit?
Oh, I wasn't talking about his karma.
Hey, check out the hat!
Wait a minute, I know that hat.
I was taken aboard that hat.
They did experiments on me.
I can't have children!
Seriously, where did you get the hat?
Ross gave it to me.
I think she looks good.
Did he buy it for you...
...or win it for you?
Excuse me,
my fashion-impaired friends...
... I'm here to tell you
hats are back.
And this time, they've ganged up
and formed one giant super-hat.
Go, go, go!
Now everybody wants to be
under the hat!
What's with all this sand?
Bob said there might be flood damage.
Either that or he has
a really big cat.
It's kind of an unusual house.
It has three beautiful bedrooms
and no baths.
But, you know, the ocean
is right there.
IKnock, knock, knock.
Hang on.
Come in, come in.
Think about it and call me back.
Are you Phoebe Abbott?
Surprise, Phoebe Abbott!
I'm your best friend's daughter!
You're lrwin's daughter?
I mean your old best friend.
Here.
-Lily? From high school? Remember?
-Oh, God, Lily. Yes.
Of course I remember Lily.
Then you must be
Phoebe, Phoebe.
She named me after you, I guess.
Wow. Well.
Look, there's Frank!
Yeah! Yes! Yes, yes!
That's my dad. That's Frank!
I'm sorry I'm getting all flingy.
Take it easy.
If you want, there's cookies.
Or sangria! I could make sangria!
Sorry. Cookies are good, thanks.
Anyway, I've been
looking for my father.
-Have you heard from him or seen him?
-Oh, no, I'm sorry.
I lost track of everybody
after high school.
Well, so tell me everything
about my parents. Everything.
Oh, well, you know,
we were always together.
-The other kids had a nickname for us.
-What was it?
The Three Losers.
Oh, poor Lily.
I heard what happened. That must
have been just terrible for you...
...Iosing your mother that way.
Yeah, no, it was great.
You know what a really good
rainy-day game is?
I mean, naked game.
We should play strip poker.
Are you crazy?
Come on. When you go away,
you have to play. It's, like, a law.
-All done.
-Thank you.
Okay. Who's next?
No way!
Come on, please. I'm bored.
You let me do it once before.
Well, if that's the rule
this weekend....
-Get away.
-Take it like a man. Come on!
Big bullies!
How are we doing?
Bored and bored.
You know what naked card game's
never boring?
So what's Phoebe like?
I'm kind, caring and sweet.
What's Monica like?
No, the other Phoebe.
The one you went to see?
I think she knows where my dad is!
Cool!
Where is he?
She was pretending she hasn't
heard from him...
...but I found this picture.
Isn't this what he would
look like now?
Totally familiar.
Why would she lie to you?
We're having dinner tomorrow.
Maybe she'll tell me then.
Maybe she just wanted
to give him time...
...to buy me presents.
I don't know.
So you're all bored?
I'll close my eyes and point
to someone. Whoever it is...
... has to think of something
fun to do. And we have to do it.
Okay! Fan out! Fan out!
You know, we could just do this!
We all have to play strip poker?
Strip Happy Days Game?
I couldn't find cards, so it was this
or Strip Bag-Of-Old-Knitting-Stuff.
Done.
"Fonzie gives you two thumbs up.
Collect two cool points."
Get five points, you get to make
someone take off one item of clothing.
It hasn't happened yet,
but we're very excited.
Okay, come on.
Daddy needs a new electromagnetic
microscope for Prehistoric Forensics.
"Take Pinky Tuscadero up
to lnspiration Point.
Collect three cool points." Yeah!
Which gives me five.
And let's see, who is gonna lose
their clothes?
I think I pick our strip poker
sponsor, Mr. Joey Tribbiani.
All right, relax. It's just a shoe.
"Your band is playing at Arnold's.
Collect three cool points."
Which means I have five and
that means I get Joey's boxers.
Fine. Gang up on me.
I got you all,
right where I want you.
Come on! Take them off!
Actually, it's kind of cold.
What if I keep them on and
give you a peek at the good stuff?
I'm gonna make more margaritas.
What are you doing?
Trying to get me drunk?
I'm just making margaritas.
Think I'll help her out.
What is going on here?
What?
You're painting his toenails.
Chasing him around the room.
Monica, please.
He's totally flirting with you too.
He is, isn't he?
I don't know. Maybe it's just
being here at the beach together...
... but it's like something
Hi, Bonnie.
My boss let me off early,
so I took the train.
What are you guys doing?
We're playing Strip Happy Days Game.
Cool! I'll catch up!
So you still don't think...
...I'm boyfriend material?
I saw you checking me out
during the game last night.
You didn't even take off your pants.
Lucky for you.
-What?
-I don't know.
Well, is everybody else having
just the best time?
Joey's asleep.
He passed out. We put sand
around him to keep him warm.
Well, I assume the happy couple
isn't up yet?
Did you guys hear them last night?
I don't know what they were doing,
but sea turtles came up to the house.
Good morning.
-How'd you sleep?
-Great.
Like a log.
Us too.
I'm going for a walk.
Good morning.
Nice breasts by the way.
Hey, what happened to you?
Oh, nothing. I just felt like
hanging out and reading.
The water was so great. We jumped
off this pier and my suit came off.
Sorry I missed that.
Joey and Chandler sure are funny.
I brought back half the beach
in my hair.
It was easier when I shaved my head.
You know, I gotta tell you...
...I just loved your look
when you were bald.
Really?
I think about shaving it
again sometimes.
Really?
You definitely should do that.
You know what? I should do it!
You know what? Thank you.
You are so cool.
Oh, stop. Go on.
-Now go shave that head.
-All right.
What's the matter?
She canceled.
My namesake canceled on me.
She claims she had to go out of town.
She's avoiding me.
She doesn't want to tell me
where my father is. She knows!
Pheebs, that sucks.
Well, don't
"Pheebs, that sucks" me yet.
-Where are you going?
-She's out of town.
Something in her house
will tell me where he is.
Some people call that
"breaking and entering."
Well, are any of those people here?
Look, I'll do something nice, okay?
I'll fill her ice trays. Good?
Hey, everybody!
Look what you did!
You wanna touch it?
No, but it's great.
Come on, touch it.
You can feel all the bones
in your skull.
I was having a little chat
with Bonnie, and guess what?
She brought up who was
behind the head-shaving idea.
And now, who was it?
Oh, that's right. It was you!
That was her idea.
I just gave her a nudge.
She said you gave her the razor.
So anyone up for a midnight dip?
-No, I'm good.
-No, thanks.
-Okay, I'll see you in a bit.
-Okay, have fun.
Come on, see?
She doesn't look that bad.
You can see the moonlight
bouncing off her head!
What were you thinking?
I don't know.
You balded my girlfriend!
All right.
Do you think it's easy for me
to see you with somebody else?
You're the one who ended it!
Because I was mad at you!
Not because I stopped loving you!
You still love me?
You still love me.
Yeah, so?
You love me.
What does this mean?
I mean, do you want
to get back together?
No! Maybe!
I don't know.
I still can't forgive you
for what you did.
But sometimes when I'm with you,
I just feel so....
What?
I just feel....
-I just
-What?
I feel
No! I don't care!
I'm not playing one-on-one strip poker
with you for practice!
But I made cards!
Good night.
I'm going upstairs.
-Good night.
Wanna play strip poker
for practice?
My ass!
Oh, it's me! It's me!
-I didn't wanna make any noise!
-Then don't break in!
-I'm sorry!
-What are you doing here?
I came to fill your ice cube tray.
What?
Okay, look.
I took this picture from your fridge.
I know that this is my father.
This is Frank Buffay, and you were
standing next to him!
I deserve to know where I came from.
So if you can help me find my father,
then you should.
Otherwise, you're just mean.
So just tell me the truth.
All right.
The man in that picture
is Chuck Mangione.
My father is Chuck Mangione?
That's just Chuck Mangione.
I sold him a house last year.
And I'm very sorry, but I really don't
know where your father is.
And that's the truth.
But you're right.
I think a person should know
where they come from.
Which is why l....
I'm your mother.
I wanted to tell you
yesterday, but I just...
...felt all floopy, and....
You guys are getting back together.
She doesn't even know what she wants.
Rachel's still mad at me.
Then you gotta back away.
You don't need that kind of hurt.
Take it from a guy who's...
... never had a long-term relationship.
I know, but I really want to go
up there and finish that kiss.
The water is great.
You should go in.
No, thanks. I just had an M&M.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Don't be too long.
Okey-dokey.
There is not one hair on that head.
It'll grow back, right?
And she's really fun, and she's cool.
And I'm finally moving on.
Getting over Rachel was so
I'm finally feeling sane.
And if I go up there...
...and I kiss her....
God, I want to kiss her!
And it doesn't work out. Do I wanna
put myself through that again?
Let me get this straight.
If you go with Bonnie, you do the
smart, healthy thing and move on.
Right? And if you go with Rachel,
Bonnie's free tonight?
Hi there.
That's that weird voice again.
Let me try it again.
You'll wanna date this next guy,
I swear!
Hi, I'm Dorf!
Your date for the evening.
Oh, come on. Dorf on dating?
That's good stuff!